lensbazaar.com 2015-05-15

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY:-**

We respect your privacy and will at all times seek to comply with privacy laws. The personal data we collect about our users shall be carefully and adequately processed, and will not be disclosed, rented or sold to third parties other than described within this privacy policy. We collect this information to be able to process your order and to offer you our newsletter and special deals when it is time to refill your order (this will include your name, date of birth, e-mail, postal addresses, credit card information and details of any prescription supplied to you by your optician or medical practitioner). You will need to give your consent before any processing takes place and your personal data will only be used for the purposes stated in these terms and conditions and or at the point of collection. We are committed to maintaining the highest standards of personal data protection and will not collect information about you without your consent.

POLICIES

Security Policy

We take the security of your information very seriously. Our E-Commerce Pay channels are assisted by CC Avenues Payment Gateway Facility which takes Credit Cards / Indian Debit Cards and also Net Banking for Indian Banks

All CC Avenues payments are directed via CC Avenues payments gateway and are said to be very safe environment of payment.

However, we do not guarantee any payment gateway as 100% Secures

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure

Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section.

Receiving our newsletter is required as part of the service that we offer. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters you may deactivate your account.

Opt-Out

We provide you the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any special offer emails from us, you may opt-out at anytime by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each email communication.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at [admin@lensbazaar.com](mailto:admin@lensbazaar.com)

Effective Date: 06/06/2012

COPYRIGHT NOTICE. **KRISHNA SUPER SPECIALITY OPTICAL CLINICS PRIVATE LIMITED**., All rights reserved. Any rights not expressly granted herein are hereby reserved.
